# Apitchaya Radchakit

Udon Thani, Thailnd 08-2497-9146 apitchaya.rchk@gmail.com https://github.com/Apitchaya-rchk

From 3+ years of teaching experience, I can work under pressure that requires adjustment and problem-solving. Besides that, I have excellent emotional control and communication skills in working with others. With a background in mathematics teaching and an interest in logic and algorithms, I am excited to explore new experiences and opportunities to work in the technology field. Being a fast learner and hard-working, I believe that I will be able to do well in this field and create amazing things. Currently, I am looking for a position as a junior software developer.

One of the best things about life is that we never have to stop learning. There are always new skills to learn and techniques for us to adopt.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Anuban Udonthani School | Nov 2020 - Aug 2021

## Government Teacher

- Plan and organize teaching in mathematics courses for children in grades 4-6 with different levels of knowledge.
- Assigned as the Finance Officer and bookkeeping on school budgets:
   Transforming the way of work by taking data from documents and processing with a computer system to reduce human error and process budgets more efficiently using Excel.
- Train teachers and school staff, including non-tech persons, to use the necessary tools and software to support online teaching during the COVID-19 pandemic.

Municipality 3 Yuwaboon Bumrung School  $\mid$  Nov 2019 - Jun 2020

# **Contract Teacher**

- Plan and organize teaching in mathematics courses for children in grades 7-9 for underprivileged and lacking educational opportunities.
- Responsible for maintaining the school's website and Facebook pages to create content and digital media.

Traimitwitthayalai School | Oct 2018 - Mar 2019

# Student Teacher (Intern)

- Plan and organize teaching for the following content.
  - Graphic design with Photoshop courses for grade 9
  - Mathematics courses for grade 11

Chulalongkorn University Demonstration Secondary School | May 2018 - Oct 2018

## Student Teacher (Intern)

- Plan and organize teaching for the following content.
  - Computing science courses for grade 10 Including doing a project on basic data analysis using MATLAB.
  - Fundamentals of using the C# courses for grade 9
  - o Mathematics courses for grade 9
- Assigned to work on the media in the school: taking pictures, recording videos, and making posters about school activities.

#### **TRAINING**

Generation Thailand | Jan 2022 - Apr 2022

# Junior Software Developer

- Practises technical skills such as HTML, Javascript, MongoDB, Node.js
- Develop the behaviours and attitudes that are important to the work that will help the job successfully.

#### **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

# Chulalongkorn University Bachelor of Education

2014 - 2019

Graduated with Honors
Field of Education Technology
Major: Education Computer,
Mathematics

## **KEY SKILL**

## Technical skills

- HTML
- Javascript
- · React.js
- Node.is
- MongoDB
- SQL

## Soft Skills

- · Problem-solving
- Communication
- Teamwork and Collaboration
- Emotional Intelligence
- · Flexibility and Adaptability
- Orientation to details
- Persistence
- Growth Mindset
- Time management.
- Curiosity and Lifelong Learning

## **INTERESTS**

- · Mechanical keyboard
- IT Gadgets
- Self-improvement
- Education
- MBTI
- HumanBehavior
- Game